⃇'
In the beginning. there was only ocean.
Until she emerged. our mother island. Teffiti.
Her heart held the power to create life itself.
And Teffiti shared it with the world.
In time. some sought to catch the heart for themselves.
For they believed if they could possess it. the power of creation would be things.
And one day. the most daring of the more.
voyaged across the vast ocean to take it.
He was a demigod of the wind and sea.
A warrior. a trickster. a shape-shifted. who could change form with the power of his magical fish hook.
And his name was Maui.
She was rumbled before we got here. right?
But without her heart. Teffiti began to crumble. giving birth to a terrible darkness.
Maui tried to escape. but was confronted by another who sought the heart.
Tekah. a demon of earth and fire.
Maui was struck from the sky. never to be seen again.
And his magical fish hook and the heart of Teffiti were lost to the sea.
Where even now. a thousand years later. Tekah and the demons of the deep still hunt for the heart.
hiding in a darkness that will continue to spring. draining the life from island after island.
And who we are all about by the blood and thirsty. inescapable jaws of death.
But one day. the heart will be found by someone who will journey beyond our wreath.
Find Maui. deliver him across the great ocean to restore the heart of Teffiti and save us all.
Whoa. whoa. whoa. Thank you. mother.
Papa! There she is. As you all know. no one goes beyond the wreath.
We are safe here. There is no darkness and there are no monsters.
I'm going! I'm going!
I sit there at no monster.
As long as we stay on our very safe island. we'll be quiet.
The natives are truly safe.
Don't worry. I'll help you.
Shoo! Shoo! Shoo! Give me a hug.
Do you want to go to the ocean?
Yeah. me too.
I'll find my friend. maybe someone's message. seems like she pursued it by finding someone's message.
The work he made for us is suddenly used as a radical multilateralency.
Oh. no. don't mind that song
Oh. don't mind that song
Vib. vib. vib. vib
Oh. I'm white though. I'm not gonna find a finder
Sound that. oh. all I can get
Are youanimate?
G site. takebababy
She tied the way.
Tell you one night
And broke her
I couldn't do nothing
No!
One
You don't go out there.
I want to listen. There's nothing beyond the wreath with storms and rough seas.
Wanna?
Mom's here.
There's my little adventure.
You're a very important sweetheart and the next great chief of our people.
And you will do wondrous things.
Can I do them in the water?
No.
Never pass the ring.
Come on.
First you'll learn where you're meant to be.
Oh. I know.
Make way. make way.
Oh. you're meant to be.
You know what you like. well. there you are.
You are your father's daughter. stubbornness and pride.
Mind what he says. but remember. you may hear a voice inside.
And if that voice starts to whisper. to follow the father's star.
Wanna let that voice inside is who you are.
Moana.
Dad. I wasn't gonna go out there.
Just doing my daily canoe inspection.
Walk with me.
I wanted to bring you here since the moment you opened your eyes.
This is a sacred place.
A place of chiefs.
Soon you will come of age and place a stone on this mountain like I did.
Like my father did.
And his mother did.
And every chief that has ever been.
And on that day when you add your stone.
you will raise this whole island higher.
You are the future of our people. Moana.
And our people are not out there.
You're right here.
It's time to start preparing to be who they need you to be.
Hi. granny!
I'll leave the way. I'll have my people to guide me
We'll fill those art futures together
Where we are. is every path leads you back to
Where you are. you can find happiness right
Where you are. you can where you are. you can where you are
I'll leave the way. you can find happiness right now
Here's my name. stay
Pa!
Thank you very much
We need to review the meaning of the word stay
Pa!
All right. let's give this stone thing a trifle up
This one says passionate
Which grow?
Over there
It's getting worse. we should clear any disease. trees. replant
Let us know if you find more
Later of the people
This is playful. fierce
It's important. Pa!
It's forever
What's wrong?
It's not just the coconuts now. it's also the catch
We drive the whole lagoon. there are no fish
They are just gone
I remember when my grandmother was chief
A hurricane kept the fish away for weeks
But they had dried fish stores and fresh coconuts
They were prepared to wait until the fish came back
And they did come back
But there is no hurricane. and even then. the lagoon was never empty
There's always a solution we just need to look for
Wow!
If the lagoon is empty. what if we fish farther out. beyond the reef?
No one goes beyond the reef
But if we can't rely on coconuts and the fish here are gone
And we're surrounded by a whole bunch
We have one rule
A rule when there is food
A rule that keeps us safe
We have to do something
I will not endanger our people
So you can run back to the water
Why not?
No. either
I wanna
I thought I'd find you here
I didn't say you should go beyond the reef because I wanna be on the ocean
I know
But you kinda do
I am trying to be what our people need.
What he needs. but it doesn't seem to be enough for him.
He was just like you. Morna.
Dad. Mm-hmm.
Drowned to the ocean. ignoring the warning. don't cross the reef.
He took a canoe.
Cross the reef and found an unfurugly sea.
Waves like mountains. just got some beg to be on that boat.
Her dad couldn't save him.
He's hoping he can save you.
Sometimes. who we wish we were and who we need to be.
it don't match up.
I've been staring at the edge of the water.
all as I can remember. never really knowing more.
I wish I could be the perfect daughter.
but I come back to the water no matter how hard I try.
Every turn I take every trail I track every path I make.
every roll leads back to the place I know.
where I cannot go. where I long to be.
I see the line where the sky meets the sea. it calls me.
and no one knows how far it goes.
If the wind in my sail on the sea stays behind me.
one day I'll know.
If I go. there's just no telling how far I'll go.
I know everybody on this island seems so happy on this island.
Everything is my design.
I know everybody on this island has a goal on this island.
so maybe I can roll with mine.
I can lead with pride. I can make a stroke.
I'll be satisfied if I play along.
but the voice inside sees a different song.
what is wrong with me.
See the line as each shines on the sea. it's blinding.
but no one knows how deep it goes.
and it seems like it's holding out to me so come find me.
And let me know what's beyond that line that I cross down.
the line where the sky meets the sea. it calls me.
and no one knows how far it goes.
If the wind in my sail on the sea stays behind me.
one day I'll know how far I'll go.
It's okay. it's okay. we're okay.
I can do this.
There's more fish beyond the rays.
There's more beyond the rays.
Okay. study?
Not bad.
Hold on.
No!
Hold on down!
Whatever just happened. blame it on the peak.
Are you gonna tell dad?
I miss mom.
I don't have to tell him anything.
He was right.
I don't belong out there.
I need to put my stone on the mountain.
Okay. have fun.
You're not gonna try and talk me out of it?
You said it's what you want.
It is.
When I die. I'm going to come back as one of these.
Whoa. I chose the wrong tip.
Why are you acting weird?
I'm the village crazy lady. that's my job.
Grandma. if there's something you want to tell me. just tell me.
Is there something you want to tell me?
There's something you want to hear.
Did this mountain get on?
You've been told all of our people's stories.
That's what.
What is this place?
Do you really think our ancestors stayed within the week?
What's in there?
The answer to the question you keep asking yourself.
Go inside. bang the drum. and find out.
Who am I meant to be?
Bang the drum.
We're in the wind and the sky when the sun is high.
We sail the land of the seas on the ocean breeze.
And like we name there is the wind.
We know who we are.
We sail across the fight of a new island everywhere we've all.
We're in the wind and when it's time to fight we'll go away.
We sail away.
We tell the stories of our elders in a never ending trail.
We were voyagers.
Brother!
I don't like water.
Why did we stop?
Now we...
When east old the heart of Teffiti. an evil began.
Te ka. a woke monster. he merged.
A canoe stopped coming back.
To protect our people. the ancient chiefs. for bed or henching. for so long we have forgotten who we are.
And now the darkness has finally found us.
It's everywhere.
The island is dying. The stories are true.
The story has just begun.
I saw you bed day more than in the water.
I thought it was a dream.
The ocean chose you to journey beyond our wreath.
Right now we deliver him across the great ocean to restore the heart of Teffiti and save us all.
Lord of light. Lord of light.
King D
That Maui lies there at the bottom of his fish hook. Follow it. and you will find him.
Dad needs to know. I'll show him the canoes. He will help.
Do what you must but hurry.
Hurry.
Par Layer the pap! C
I know how we can fix this. We can find Maui. I have the heart. If we follow the stars.
the hook. there's canoes. Dad. we were voyagers once. We can voyage again.
You think you're the first one that grandma's taking on that place?
You knew?
Our ancestors closed that cave for a reason they were trying to protect us.
Dad. you told me to help our people. Ignoring who we are isn't helping our people.
We have to find Maui. Restore the heart. Our island is dying. We can't do nothing.
This is nothing.
Two!
It's your mother!
Go!
Not now. again.
You must.
The ocean shows you.
Follow the fish hook.
And when you find Maui. you grab him by the ear.
And you say. I am Moana of Mutinui.
You will board my butterm.
Sail across the sea.
You will be able to see the sun.
Moana of Mutinui.
You will board my butterm.
Sail across the sea.
And restore the heart of dead feet.
I can't leave you.
There is nowhere.
You can go.
That I want to be with you.
There is a line with the sky.
It's the sea and it calls me.
But no one knows how far it goes.
All the time wondering where I need to be is behind me.
I'm on my own.
So roll that down.
Every turn I take. every trail I track is a choice I make.
Now I can't turn back from the great unknown.
Or I go alone where I long to be.
See her light up the night in the sea.
And she calls me.
And guess I go.
I can't go.
There is a moon in the sky and the wind is behind me.
And so no no.
How far it goes.
I am one of Mutinui.
You will board my boat.
Sail across the sea.
And restore the heart of tiffy tea.
I am one of Mutinui.
You will board my boat.
Sail across the sea.
Hey!
See?
See. you're all right.
Look.
The ocean is a friend of mine.
Hey. hey.
Please tell me you brought your own food.
I am one of Mutinui.
You will board my boat.
Sail across the sea.
And restore the heart of tiffy tea.
No. no. no. no. no.
No. come on.
I am one of Mutinui.
You will board my boat.
What?
No. no. no. no.
It's okay.
Just a little rain.
No!
Ocean! Please help me!
I am one of Mutinui.
Um. what?
I said help me. Enthith.
Red King. my boat.
Not helping.
This peony.
All day.
And worse stuff too. so.
Mollie.
Mollie?
Demi got it for wind and sea.
I am one of Mutinui.
You'll board... no.
You will board my boat.
Yeah!
Boat!
The gods have given me a boat!
In a tiny little human.
Well. hello. tiny human.
Not too sure why they thought I needed you.
You can take back the little human.
Oh. I'm gonna eat whatever that is.
It's a chicken.
His name is Heihue.
His name is Yum Yum when he goes in my tum tum.
Mollie.
Shape shifter.
Demi got it for wind and sea.
Yes.
I am one of Mutinui.
Hero of men.
Huh?
So it goes like this.
Mollie.
Shape shifter.
Demi got it for wind and sea.
Hero of men.
Ah!
Women.
Women too.
Men and women.
Not a girl guy thing.
Two all.
I think you're doing great.
Start at the top.
Three. two. one.
Hit it.
I am watching.
I am.
I am the one.
No. I am.
You're completely overwhelmed.
But don't worry.
Mollie always has time for his fans.
Oh. I'm...
That's okay.
May I see the oar?
Thank you.
Alright.
You know. before I write anything.
I want to know about you.
Tell me your hopes.
Tell me your dreams.
Well. I guess I kind of...
Time's up.
I'm going to go back to Moana.
Figure out your dreams and...
Follow them.
Oh.
Chicken just pecked my foot.
He wants one too.
Or to graph.
Or chicken.
Look at that face.
I know it's not every day you get a chance to see your hero.
You are not my hero.
And I'm not here so you can sign my oar.
And here. because you stole...
This.
The heart of Tiffy T.
And you will board my boat.
Sail across the sea and put it back.
Yeah.
You know. it's kind of crazy because it almost sounds like you don't like me.
which is impossible.
Because...
Look at me.
I have been stranded on this island for over a thousand years.
because I was trying to get that heart as a gift for you mortals.
So. what I believe you are trying to say...
Is I appreciate you.
What?
I'm grateful for you.
That's all right.
I'll stop messing with you.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
No. no. I didn't.
I wasn't saying...
Okay. okay.
I see what's happening.
Yeah.
You're face to face with greatness and it's strange.
You don't even know how you feel.
It's adorable.
Well. it's nice to see that humans never change.
Open your eyes.
Let's begin.
Yes. it really is. Maui.
Breathe it in.
I know it's a lot.
The hair is a bond.
When you're staring at a dreamy god.
What can I say except you're welcome.
For the tides to sun the sky.
Hey. it's okay.
It's okay.
You're welcome.
I'm just an ordinary jelly guy.
Hey. what has two thumbs and food of the sky?
Why you were wildly yay high this sky.
When the night's got cold. who stole you?
Fire from down below.
You're looking at him. yo.
Oh. also at last so the sun.
You're welcome to stretch your days and bring you fun.
Also I harnessed the breeze.
You're welcome to build your sails and check your dreams.
So what can I say except you're welcome.
For the islands I pulled from the sea.
There's no need to pray it's okay.
You're welcome.
I guess that's just my way to be me.
Well. welcome to figure it out.
Honestly. I could go on and on.
I could explain every natural phenomenon.
The tide. the grass. the ground.
Although it was Maui just messing around.
I put a nail. I buried a tuss.
It's better to treat now you've got coconuts.
What's the lesson?
What does it take away?
Oh. so Maui went. he's on a breakaway.
And the tapestry here on my skin is the map of the victories I win.
What?
Why did I make everything happen?
Look at that meany-nilly now.
We're just digging the tap and singing its graphic.
It's not because she's bobbing victory.
Laughing. bringing the chorus back in.
Well. anyway. let me say you're welcome.
For the wonderful world you know.
Hey. it's okay. it's okay. you're welcome.
Come to think the beat. I gotta go.
Hey. it's okay. let's say you're welcome.
Cause I'm gonna need that boat.
I'm sailing away. away. you're welcome.
Cause Maui can do anything but boats.
You're welcome. you're welcome.
And thank you.
Hey. you lying sneaking son of a...
Beach. I'll smell you later.
I don't know how many you live at below.
Pa pa.
Ow. what?
Well. I'm not gonna go to Tefidi with some kid. I'm going to get my hook.
But hey. you already have yours. I'm not Maui without mine.
And if you keep it up. I got a cave for you to go in.
Boat snoot!
Come on.
Oh. that's what I remember.
Ow!
She's fine.
Look. she's going to have an entire island to herself. and she's going to love it.
And I'm going to love you.
In my belly.
Let's fatten you up. drumstick.
Wow! You are dumb. Good chicken.
Ahh! So close.
I could watch that all day.
Enjoy the island.
Maui.
Ow.
Hey! No! You have to destroy the horse.
Bye-bye.
Hey!
The kid? No?
No. I'm having to get out of here.
And she's back.
Close your eyes.
I am one of...
No! I'm getting...
Good job. me.
It was Moana. right of...
Want to know.
Restore the heart.
I'll take my chances with the monsters.
Alright. I'm out.
I thought we were friends.
Oh!
What's wrong with you?
There's nothing wrong with me. I'm awesome. I've endured.
Are you?
No.
No. no. no. Don't do that.
Afraid?
No. no. no. Afraid?
Maui?
No.
I don't do fear.
That thing is not a heart. It's a curse.
In the second I took it. I got blown out of the sky and I lost my hook. Get it away from me!
Yes.
Yes. that's enough.
I am a demi-god.
And I will smite you. And you don't want any other smote.
Yeah. you. just like you don't want that. That thing doesn't create life. It's a beacon of death.
And if you don't put it away. then bad things are going to happen.
Put this away.
Yes.
The heart.
Don't do that.
Afraid?
Don't tempt the gods. That way you're going to get us killed.
I'm going to get us two tech feet teeth so you can put it back. Thank you. You're welcome.
Oh.
You know. if I were wrong just once. I would be humble. I promise.
What is that?
Kakamora.
Kakamora?
Poisonous little pillagers.
They look kind of cute.
Really? Define cute.
I wonder what they're here for.
You are going to get the psyched one. I'm not afraid of reluctance.
You are gonna get the scotch of me.
You have faith in yourself.
Don't move.
You will march.
You are not voting.
No.
I won.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
Your Pur lineup's followed by a bad game.
She doesn't work on this thing with me.
Mother...
How rude you can't shoot this tin.
Vi...
So there aren't these things...
I don't mean one of them who's here to listen to you.
You should not Hold the pistol on to them.
Maybe that would be good.
Colopy.
No. no.
Justin. because not the victim is left with the Wraps whistling And I don't remember without Cas beat.
Yeah.
Can't you shave. Chip. or something?
No man to cook. no man to power.
No!
I'm although I will not die. but I will go on your way.
In theaters!
Hey-hey!
Give this back!
Pub-O-E. they took the harp!
Time.
We have to get it back!
Pub-O-E!
Told you it was cursed!
Alright!
There! Right there!
Aah!
Aye!
You're turning!
Yeah. you can't!
What are you doing?
Escaping?
The heart is that way!
We'll never get it.
Okay!
I'll do it!
Hey. what have I got a stairwind?
They're just gonna kill ya!
I'm gonna need that heart.
Going?
Yeah!
Ha ha ha!
Oh!
Aah!
Oh my!
Ha ha ha!
Aah!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
What?
Whoa!
Got it!
Ha ha ha ha!
Go on. go on. go on!
Yay!
That was incredible!
We did it!
We!
By we. you mean mow-wee!
Because we didn't do anything.
I did it!
By the way. mow-wee's not spelled with a we. it's spelled with an I.
We are alive!
But I'm still not taking that thing back.
Why not?
Because in order to get to Tefiti. you gotta go through Taka. a lava monster.
You ever defeat a lava monster. Princess?
No!
Have you?
You know what?
I'm just gonna say it.
You both are very bad.
Now where should be me?
You want me to believe that of your entire island. your chief. he picked you.
He picked us a strong word.
I'm not going on a suicide mission with some mortal.
In order to restore the heart. you need me and me says no.
I'm getting my hook.
End of discussion.
You'd be a hero again.
That's what you're all about. right?
Little girl. I am a hero.
Well. maybe you were.
But a lot's changed in a thousand years.
Now you're the guy who stole the heart of Tefiti. the guy who cursed the whole world.
You're no wonder. Earl.
Ha! Ha! Ha!
That's impossible!
I'm everyone's hero.
Oh. nice.
Just gang up on the demigod.
Look. I promise.
You put this back. save the world.
You'd be everyone's hero.
Forever.
Sounds good. right?
Oh. wow.
I saw a basic wow.
Look at the definition. this girl's.
It's true. I do have a beautiful hair.
If I do this. then you and your people will address me as a hero.
I'm not a hero.
Act like one and I might.
Deal.
You can't get rid of me.
Worth a shot.
I guess you're coming.
Okay.
To the lair of Tama Toa.
If anyone has my hook. it's that beady-eyed scavenger.
You could teach me sailing.
This isn't sailing. Princess.
It's called wayfinding.
It's about seeing where you're going in your mind.
It's about knowing where you are and knowing where you've been.
I'm not a princess.
I'm the daughter of the chief.
Ha! It's the same thing.
No.
Yes. if you wear a skirt and if you have a little animal sidekick.
you're a princess. Princess.
I'm not a wayfinder.
Unless you can find a way to be less annoying.
Oh!
Really?
Blow dart to my buttjig.
Ha!
If you can talk. you can teach.
I am a demi-god.
Wayfinding. Lesson one. Hit it.
Slack out the tricing.
No. Not that one. The other one.
No. The ground roping.
You're measuring the stars. not giving the sky a high-five.
If you feel the water and it's warm.
it means we're going the right way.
It's cold.
Wait. it's getting warmer.
Ew! That's disgusting!
What is wrong with you?
Uh-huh.
Right here.
What?
That?
Oh!
Mom?
Let's love Butter Cup.
We're here.
Damn!
Are you sure this guy's got your hook?
Tomatoa is not a guy.
Anything that's cool that sinks to the bottom of the ocean he collects in.
There's nothing cooler than my hook.
Except maybe my face.
Or these muscles.
I'm getting my hook.
You start singing now.
I'm going to throw up everywhere.
So. not seeing an entrance?
The entrance will only appear after the human sacrifice.
Kidding?
You need to lighten up.
I'm going to throw up everywhere.
So. not seeing an entrance?
The entrance will only appear after the human sacrifice.
Kidding?
You need to lighten up.
Oh. wow.
Oh. yeah.
Don't worry.
It's a lot farther down than it looks.
Damn!
I'm going to throw up there.
Oh. wow.
Oh. yeah.
Don't worry.
It's a lot farther down than it looks.
Damn!
Oh. wow.
Dammit!
I'm still falling.
Crazy!
No.
The ocean chose you for a reason.
Yes. my!
Still falling!
I can't hear this.
No!
I'm scared!
You lived! Go. you! How's my hair look? Don't answer that. You know what? Maybe you could jump back up and get out of here while the ground folks go to work.
You lived! Go you. How's my hair look? Don't answer that.
You know what? Maybe you could jump back up and get out of here while the
Gromfos go to work.
Stop trying to ditch me. I can do stuff.
Yeah? Like what?
Like I just jumped into that monster mountain and I didn't die.
And I got you off that island. No one else did that?
So what's our plan?
Oh. you're still here. I was planning on doing it all alone. but I'm not that
lucky today.
Now we.
I can be useful if you'd let me.
Okay.
Really?
You know. sometimes in life. You're the hero and sometimes...
You're the bait.
Wait. what?
What?
Wow. I'm shiny. glittery. cave. Sparkle. sparkle.
What are you going to. a funeral? Do you know how I'm convincing you sound right now?
You have to commit. Say the other line that I wrote. Have fun with it. You got it?
Wow! I'm sparkly treasure. Look over here!
Do it again. but more convincing.
Sparkle!
Sideways.
Sparkle.
Smarter.
Sparkle?
You're butchering the lies.
Sparkle!
You sound like a drunk. I don't even know what there was.
Way too unlikable.
Sparkle?
It all sucks.
I can't do this anymore.
Yes. you can.
You be the bait. I'm just going to go up there and get it.
Look. you go up there. you're going to get killed.
At least this would be over.
Okay. listen. If you run into him. you have to distract him.
And remember. he loves to brag about how great he is.
No. you two must get along well.
Not really. Not since I ripped off his leg.
You ripped off his...
Maui!
That's curious.
You're a human.
What are you doing down here?
In the realm of monsters.
Pick an eye. babe.
I can't concentrate on what I'm saying.
Pick one.
You're a funny looking thing. but this necklace.
Don't do my promise!
Forget my grandma!
Well. I ate my grandma.
And I'm going to get you.
And it took a week because she was absolutely humongous.
Why are you here?
For you!
Because you're so amazing to meet you.
Go on.
We mortals have heard a lot about the crab who ate his nana and became a legend.
Wait a minute.
Are you just trying to get me to talk about myself?
Because if you are...
I will gladly do so.
In song form.
Okay. everyone. This is why we rehearsed.
Life.
Music.
I did it.
Well. some of Tor has always been this clown.
I was a tribe. little crab boy.
Now I know I can be happy as a clown.
Because I'm beautiful. baby.
Well...
Did you get it. Seth?
It's Ontario High.
People you are on the inside.
I need three words to tell her argument to call.
You're granny live.
A brother but a shiny.
Not a blemish on the surface. not a spare.
Double check is everything.
Shiny!
I was farmed like a wealthy woman's neck.
Just a sec. don't you know.
Fish is dumb. dumb. dumb.
They chase anything that she loves.
To Guinness.
And if I come. dumb. dumb.
To the water from the river.
Fish Guinness.
I just love free food.
And you look like speed boots.
Crank-cank!
I'm back.
It's Maui time!
What do you say. little buddy?
Giant hunk?
Coming up.
Yes. I'm holding it right.
I know what I'm doing.
I didn't order Calamawi.
Well. it's Maui's having trouble with his love.
You're the two semidem in me. god.
You want a terrible performance.
Get out!
Get it.
You don't bring it like a youth dude.
Oh man.
Yes. I have to give you credit for my start.
And your tattoos on the outside.
For just like you. I've made myself work if I'm.
I'll never hide.
I come to do shiny.
Watch me dance like a diamond in the rug.
I'm stuck. I'm stuck. I'm stuck.
You still shining.
I send your armies. but there'll never be enough.
My shelter's all in the morning.
You can try. try. try.
I'm like a constant demi car.
I want to be the decker part.
Look it up.
You will die. die. die.
Now it's time for me to take a part.
You're aching heart.
Far from the ones who were banding.
You're chasing the love of these youth.
Too many. you feel wanted.
You try to be tough.
But your armor's just not hard enough.
I am.
And now it's time to take your highness.
Ever since no one's so shiny.
So get in because it's the last you'll ever see.
Say a few more. now be unfinished.
I need it.
Now I need you to prepare a final plea.
Just for me.
You'll never be quite as shiny.
You wish you were a nicer. shiny.
Hey!
I got something shiny for you.
A lot of tiffy.
Don't give it to me. kid.
You want it?
Come and get it.
You can't run from me.
Oh. you can.
He keeps surprising me.
There's only so far you can get on those two little legs.
You chipped bad luck.
The power of creation.
Taracostation.
Oh. will it?
Where is it?
Come on. tiffy.
Time to go. shall we?
What about the heart?
Peeking at it.
I've got a better one.
Yes. it is mine. peeks.
Wait a minute.
I see.
She's taking the barnacle and she's covered it in bioluminescent algae as a diversion.
Come back here.
There is no escape.
Oh. there is one escape.
Hey. did you like the song?
Did you have any notes or feedback?
Oh.
Maui.
Listen. I really appreciate what you did down there.
That took guts.
And I...
Oh. I get it.
Big. tough. handsome guy gets emotional.
And what do you do?
You laugh in his face.
God. son.
Oh. no.
Is there something on my face?
In my teeth?
Is there something in my teeth?
No. no. no. no. no. no. no!
Shark head!
I like this part.
I mean. the nice part.
I was not making fun of the shark portion.
Look. the point is you did me a solid.
but you almost died and I couldn't even beat the dumb crack.
So chances of beating Takah are bup-kiss.
This mission has no chance because you're still you and I have a shark head.
Hey. it's okay. it's okay.
There's no wind.
We're dead soon.
Because we're both gonna die on this boat.
Hey.
Maybe try it with a smile.
Giant hawk.
Maui's gonna do the dead man's float.
Hey!
Why are you being like this?
We millow.
Both of you.
We mill.
How do you get your tattoos?
They just show up.
When I earn them. they just show up.
How did you get that one?
That one's man's discovery of Nanya.
What's Nanya?
Nanya business.
I'm just gonna keep asking.
Drop it.
Why was that crab poking-
That goth.
What is he?
No!
What is it?
Don't want to talk about it.
Get it back!
If you don't want to talk. that's fine.
But my island. my people.
My family.
They won't survive if we don't make it.
I want to help.
If you let me.
I wasn't born a demigod.
I had human parents.
Decided they didn't want me.
So they threw me in the ocean.
Like I was nothing.
Somehow I washed ashore.
Found by the gods.
They gave me my hook.
They made me mowy.
So back to the humans I went.
I gave them everything.
Islands.
Fire.
Coconut.
I gave them anything they ever wanted.
You took the heart for us.
You did everything for us.
So we'd love you.
Yes.
It was never enough.
The ocean chose you too.
That should take away.
Because it saw someone worthy of being saved.
And what am I now?
You're mowy.
The gods didn't make that true.
You did.
Okay.
Not in front of the cast.
Currently. I have adjacent
books. books. books
We have to go.
Go.
Oh. my man.
Basically. that compret Raven Mode.
or get himWouldule sunset over the morning.
And then you're going to the tournament
where you couldn't figure out how
Stylesnake is to trick me to normalize
I'm gonna be buying tea.
I know what to do.
They're not anymore too good news.
Thank you.
Glad you enjoyed it.
However it felt perfect.
insists that all phoneticuelos are very prepared.
Assures this 1000 GPA will be provided.
It's always aYet in your series for yourself.
Because it's 1000 per minute.
Remember ever possible to enter a circle.
Do theMO will be available at 10 in the right portion.
silver if you Fikshante.
I'm not here. I'm not here
I'm not here
I figured it out
You know the ocean would love when I would pull up the islands
Your ancestors would voyage her seas and find them
That necklace you're wearing. that belonged to Tal'Tha'vassa
First master wayfinder. he knew no two voyages were the same. different every time
A true wayfinder. we'll see all the water
As a bridge. I'm not a barrier
And if I were the ocean. I couldn't find a better curly haired sidekick having non-princess
To start voyaging again
That is the nicest thing you've ever said to me. probably should have saved it for Tifiti
I did
You can do this. you're Maui
That's true
It's my way to hide
Go save the world
Maui
We need to pull back now
What are you doing?
Finding you a way in. now's our chance
Turn around
No!
We're not gonna make it!
Yes we will!
We wanna stop!
I can do it!
Get out of here!
Are you okay?
Maui?
I told you to turn back
I thought we could make it
We?
What?
I thought I could make it
Okay
I'll find a way to fix your hook
The gods made my hook
You can't fix it
Next time I'll be more careful
There's no next time
But now we know TikTok can't follow us into the water
We can find another way around
There is no other way. I'm not going back
Take a look at my hook
One more hit and it's over
But my people. my islands
Without my hook
I am nothing
We're only here cause you stole the heart in the first place
No
We're here
Because the ocean told you
That you are special
And you believed it
I am one of much enough
Goodbye more
You will sail across the sea and restore
I'm not killing myself so you can prove you're something you're not
The ocean chose me
It chose us
It chose wrong
Goodbye. Maui
Maui
No. no!
No. don't go!
Maui
Ocean. why did you bring me here?
I was never the right person
You should choose someone else
Please
I'm not going to go to the water
You're long ways past the wreath
I guess I chose the right tattoo
Oh.
I tried.
I hope I can do it.
I can't do it.
If you're ready to go home. I will be with you.
Why do you hesitate?
I don't know.
I know a girl from an island.
She stands upon from the ground.
She loves the sea and her people.
She makes her whole family proud.
Sometimes the world seems against you.
The journey may leave us calm.
But scars can heal and reveal just where you are.
The people you love will change you.
The things you have learned will guide you.
And nothing on earth can silence.
But quiet voice still inside you.
And when that voice starts to whisper.
Moana. you've come so far.
Moana. listen.
Do you know who you are?
Who am I?
I am a girl who loves my island.
And the girl loves the sea.
It calls me.
I am the daughter of the village chief.
We are descended from four years.
We'll find a way across the world.
They call me.
I've delivered us to where we are.
I have journeyed farther in.
I am everything I've learned and lost.
Till it calls me.
And the call is to help every village since I'm with me.
It's like the time always coming and raising.
I will care for you here.
But how are you remembering me?
Let the boy play.
I know the way.
I am Moana.
Moana. yeah. no.
Yeah. yeah. no.
I am Moana of Moana.
Moana of Moana.
The sail across the sea.
Restore the heart of Tefi Tien.
We have to lure Tefi away and slip past.
Because it can't follow us through the water.
Tefi Tien.
None of which you understand because you are a chicken.
I am a chicken.
All right. Tefi.
Try and catch me.
I am a chicken.
I'm a chicken.
Don't call me.
No!
And you don't know!
Come on.
Hey. you.
Nice work.
Defeated.
No!
You came back.
I never should have left.
But your hook. One more hit.
Sir. God's gotta catch me first.
Mal.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Let's do this.
Hey. take off!
Bring it on!
Get off!
Pull on him!
Oh no.
Defeated.
She's gone.
Check off!
I'm here.
The ocean shows you.
Let her come to me.
I'm here.
I've crossed the horizon to find you.
I know you're one day out.
They have stolen the heart from inside you.
But this does not define you.
I'm one day out.
This is not who you are.
You know who you are.
Who you truly are.
Defeated.
Yeah.
Not bad.
Chicken lives.
I think.
You're hooked.
Hook or no?
I'm still Maui.
Hey!
Defeated!
How you been?
Me Maui.
We met back in the...
What I think he's trying to say.
What I did was wrong.
And I clearly have a lot of stuff that I need to work out from my past.
Issues. things like that.
Just a humble demi-god trying to find his way.
It's no excuse.
I am sorry.
Truly.
I'm sorry.
Go ahead.
It would be rude to refuse a gift from a goddess.
It's back. baby!
Yeah!
Where am I?
Right now. I am grateful.
Thank you.
I'm gonna miss you. Jumpstick.
You know. I'm up to noise that way.
You should come visit.
I would love to.
Well. we'd be happy to have you.
Anytime.
Plus. my people could use a master wayfinder.
They already helped one.
Mwah!
Hey!
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'll see you out there. Mwah.
I'll see you out there.
TAP!
Ooh!
Here you go!
handed face.
Turns back when she goes past EmTimul Zack and I'm Chantelle.
Now we're out there with you.
We'll becked aored as the chase of death and we'll open the invite for you.
Buback me. Haven't you ever hurt my makeup?
It's too late.
See you later.Cs.
I know.
Love Wanda!
Love Wanda VS The VI Agency Palae
AND
Okay okay yeah next time you do come
We are the world's world's world.
One of Montanueux. you raise our whole island higher
and take every one of our people and ancestors. the father.
Say it for I. Maia.
Ma naya o lita toolama.
read chan
And we're going to be the leader of the land
So come to the land of the land
Hallelujah!
Ye-a!
We said of course to find
We're a new island everywhere we roam
All real world
We keep our island in our mind
And when it's time to find home. we know go well
All real world
We are glorious. free in every sign
We tell the stories of our elders in a never-ending tale
And we're here to find the way
And when it's time to find the way
We know the way